ZAIN MUSHTAQ

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

+923095911378 Lahore,Pakistan www.linkedin.com/in/zainmushtaq

ABOUT

I have more than a year of experience in Backend Development, PHP, Laravel,CodeIgniter HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery, JSON, MySQL, API, Power APPS, HMIS A young, evangelistic and inventive individual having an aim for achieving the highest standards in work. A team player, going to adapt expertness. My goal is to utilize my skills to achieve more expertise whereas enhancing the company's productivity and name. Quick learner with strong analytical thinking. Interested in Development.

PROFESSIONAL SKILL

• Mobile App Technologies: POWER APPS

• Backend Technology: PHP Laravel, Codeignitor

Web Technologies: HTML5, CSS5, Tailwind, React Js, JavaScript, Jquery

Database: MySQL

• Enterprise Systems: ERP, HMIS

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science (BSCS)

University of Lahore

2022

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer

Fatima Memorial Hospital

Mar 2024-Present

- Designed and implemented a Power App to verify employee discounts on Outpatient (OPT) and Inpatient (IPT) services, enhancing efficiency and accuracy in discount management.
- Provide ongoing support and maintenance for ERP and Hospital Management Information System (HMIS) solutions, ensuring seamless integration and optimal performance.

Backend Developer

Freelancer Mar 2023-Feb 2024

- Developed a comprehensive Fuel Management System for Almeraj Groups using PHP CodeIgniter.
- Designed and implemented the system's architecture, ensuring scalability and performance. https://www.almerajgroups.com/.
- Development of Laravel APIs for a Coach Analysis Platform
- Built and maintained Laravel APIs to manage teams, players, coaches, and videos.

Frontend Developer

Snexus Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

• I worked their as UI Developer, My responsibility is to convert PSD to HTML, HTML5/CSS3/JS and Rect is Framework, Front End Development.